{
    "subject": "Violant_of_Bar",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "John_I_of_Aragon",
    "human_readable": "Violant of Bar is married to John I of Aragon.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9871205687522888,
            "question": "Was there a marriage between Violant of Bar and John I of Aragon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9782278537750244,
            "question": "Is there a known marital connection between Violant of Bar and John I of Aragon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9425103664398193,
            "question": "Is Violant of Bar related to John I of Aragon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9265984892845154,
            "question": "Who is married to John I of Aragon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9263806343078613,
            "question": "To whom is Violant of Bar married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9115946292877197,
            "question": "Who was John I of Aragon married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.91081303358078,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Violant of Bar and John I of Aragon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7972570657730103,
            "question": "What is the name of the woman married to John I of Aragon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7529569864273071,
            "question": "What is the name of John I of Aragon's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7032344341278076,
            "question": "Who is Violant of Bar?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Violant of Bar is married to John I of Aragon.",
            "html": "yago_26245_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of John I of Aragon's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_26245_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the woman married to John I of Aragon?",
            "html": "yago_26245_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the relationship between Violant of Bar and John I of Aragon?",
            "html": "yago_26245_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26245_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26245_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26245_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26245_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26245_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26245_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26245_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26245_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26245_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26245_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe documents mention that Yolande of Aragon (also known as Violant) was the daughter of John I of Aragon and his wife Violant of Bar. In addition, another document states that Yolande of Aragon married Louis II of Anjou, King of Naples, but also mentions that she had a previous marriage to John, Duke of Girona (also known as John I of Aragon), making it clear that the two documents are referring to the same person."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Yolande (Violant) of Bar was married to John, Duke of Girona, who later became the King of Aragon. This supports the statement that Violant of Bar is married to John I of Aragon."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}